http://www.eacr.org/privacy

Cookies
This website uses cookies to improve your user experience.By using the site, you agree to our use of cookies.Click here for more information about how we use cookies.
OK
Please select:« Return to page Member LoginHomeAboutAbout the EACRFrequently Asked Questions (FAQ)GovernanceBoardAdvisory CouncilStanding CommitteesStrategic PlanConstitutionMember InvolvementMembershipBecome a memberBenefits of membershipMember loginEACR AmbassadorsReward PointsResources for AmbassadorsAffiliated National SocietiesEventsAll ConferencesEACR CongressEACR ConferencesEACR WebinarsAdvertise your conferenceMember ResourcesFind a CollaborationVirtual events video archiveCOVID-19 resourcesMy MembershipMagazineMagazineFunding & AwardsTravel FellowshipsMeeting Bursaries Mike Price Gold Medal AwardPrevious winnersThe Pezcoller Foundation-EACR Rising Star AwardThe Pezcoller Foundation-EACR
Translational Cancer Researcher AwardThe Pezcoller-Marina Larcher Fogazzaro-EACR Women in Cancer Research AwardJobs & GrantsLatest jobs and grantsAdvertise your opportunityPartnersHow to partner with usSponsorship and ExhibitionIndustry PartnersStrategic PartnershipsAmerican Association for Cancer Research (AACR)The European Academy of Cancer SciencesEuropean Society for Medical Oncology (ESMO)European Society of Oncologic Imaging (ESOI)International Association for the Study of Lung Cancer (IASLC)The Metastasis Research Society (MRS)The CAREFOR ProjectThe Organisation of European Cancer Institutes (OECI)The Pezcoller FoundationWorld Cancer Research DayWorldwide Cancer ResearchOther partnershipsMake a donationContactEACR TeamContact formFrequently Asked Questions (FAQ)Make a donation
Member log in
Search
Subscribe
Follow us
Welcome to the European Association for Cancer ResearchEurope’s membership association for cancer researchers
Menu
AboutAbout the EACRFrequently Asked Questions (FAQ)GovernanceMembershipBecome a memberMember loginEACR AmbassadorsAffiliated National SocietiesEventsAll ConferencesEACR CongressEACR ConferencesEACR WebinarsAdvertise your conferenceMember ResourcesFind a CollaborationVirtual events video archiveCOVID-19 resourcesMy MembershipMagazineMagazineFunding & AwardsTravel FellowshipsMeeting Bursaries Mike Price Gold Medal AwardThe Pezcoller Foundation-EACR Rising Star AwardThe Pezcoller Foundation-EACR
Translational Cancer Researcher AwardThe Pezcoller-Marina Larcher Fogazzaro-EACR Women in Cancer Research AwardJobs & GrantsLatest jobs and grantsAdvertise your opportunityPartnersHow to partner with usIndustry PartnersStrategic PartnershipsMake a donationContactEACR TeamContact formFrequently Asked Questions (FAQ)Make a donation
Website Privacy & Cookies
Cookies and our Website Privacy Policy
Click here to see our general Privacy Policy
What are cookies?
Cookies are small text files that web sites often store on the computer hard drives of visitors to their sites. They are widely used in order to make web sites work, or work better, as well as to provide information to the owners of the site. A cookie often contains a unique number, which can be used to recognise your computer when a user of your computer returns to a website that it visited previously.
How does the EACR use cookies?
We use cookies to enhance the online experience of our visitors and to better understand how our sites are used. Cookies may tell us, for example, whether you have visited our site before or whether you are a new visitor.
Measuring website usage (Google Analytics)
We use Google Analytics to collect information about how people use this site. We do this to make sure it’s meeting its users’ needs and to understand how we could do it better.
Google Analytics stores information about what pages you visit, how long you are on the site, how you got here and what you click on. We do not collect or store your personal information (e.g. your name or address) so this information cannot be used to identify who you are. We do not allow Google to use or share our analytics data with third parties.
Highlighting menus and logging onto the website
If you log into this website (to update your details, carry out a purchase etc.) then we store any details that we need to on our server. To link your "session" data on our server with your browser session a small cookie is placed in your browser - containing an anonymised link to the session. As soon as you close your browser this session cookie is deleted.
We determine that both these types of cookies are essential to the running of the website.
Links to other Websites
We will refer to or establish relations with companies, organisations and public bodies that will enable you to access their websites directly from our website.
Each company, organisation or public body operates its own policy regarding the sale of personal data and the use of cookies. If you have a particular interest in, or concern regarding the way your data will be used then you are advised to read the Privacy Statement on the relevant website.
We will try to provide you with links to high quality, reputable websites which we believe will be of interest and relevant to you, but please note that such third party websites are not under our control and we do not contribute to the content of such websites.
When you click through to any of these websites you leave the area controlled by the EACR. We cannot accept responsibility for any issues arising in connection with the third party's use of your data, the website content or the services offered to you by these websites.
Your rights
You have the right to choose whether to accept these cookies. You can exercise this right by amending or setting the controls on your browser to reflect your cookie preferences.
However, please note that if you choose to refuse cookies you may not be able to use the full functionality of this website.
Changing your cookie preferences
The "Help" menu in the toolbar of most web browsers will tell you how to change your browser's cookie settings, including how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, and how to disable cookies altogether.
An online guide is available if you have difficulties trying to change your browser settings.
Additional references
Further information about cookies and how to control their use is available from All About Cookies and Your Online Choices.
Policy Changes
Any changes to this policy made by the EACR will be posted here and will take effect immediately. This policy was last updated on 24 May 2018.
See also
Our General Privacy Policy
Payment, Refund and Cancellation Policy
Share this page
Industry Partners
The EACR is grateful for the continued support of its Industry Partners:
About us
Join now
Contact us
Site map
Terms of use
Privacy & Cookies
EACR is a registered charity in England and Wales (1171827) and a company limited by guarantee (07682372). Registered address: Sir Colin Campbell Building, University of Nottingham Innovation Park, Triumph Road, Nottingham, NG72TU, UK.
© 2007 - 2020 The European Association for Cancer Research. All rights reserved.
Membership website design by Peter Bourne Communications
